{
  "decks": [
    {
      "name": "React Router",
      "description": "React Router is a collection of navigational components that compose declaratively with your application.",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "name": "BTS Trivia",
      "description": "What are the real names of the members of K-pop phenomenon, BTS?"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "name": "Numbers",
      "description": "Counting is fun!"
    },
    {
      "name": "Japanese",
      "description": "Domo origato, Mr. Roboto",
      "id": 16
    },
    {
      "name": "Korean",
      "description": "K-everything is life!",
      "id": 17
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "What path will match the follow Route?\n<Route>\n  <NotFound />\n</Route>",
      "back": "All paths. A route with no path matches all URL's",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "front": "What does <Switch> do?",
      "back": "Renders the first matching child <Route> ",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "front": "",
      "back": "",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "front": "RM's real name",
      "back": "Kim Namjoon",
      "deckId": 7,
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "front": "Jin's real name",
      "back": "Kim Seokjin",
      "deckId": 7,
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "front": "J-Hope's real name",
      "back": "Jung Ho-seok",
      "deckId": 7,
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "front": "Suga's real name",
      "back": "Min Yoongi",
      "deckId": 7,
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "front": "V's real name",
      "back": "Kim Taehyung",
      "deckId": 7,
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "front": "Jimin's real name",
      "back": "Park Jimin",
      "deckId": 7,
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "front": "Jungkook's real name",
      "back": "Jeon Jeonggkuk",
      "deckId": 7,
      "id": 13
    },
    {
      "front": "What is the fan-made BTS chant?",
      "back": "Kim Namjoon,\nKim Seokjin,\nMin Yoongi,\nJung Ho-seok,\nPark Jimin,\nKim Taehyung,\nJeon Jungkook,\nBTS!",
      "deckId": 7,
      "id": 14
    },
    {
      "front": "What",
      "back": "Nani",
      "deckId": 16,
      "id": 18
    },
    {
      "front": "Hello",
      "back": "Konichiwa",
      "deckId": 16,
      "id": 19
    },
    {
      "front": "Thank you",
      "back": "Origato",
      "deckId": 16,
      "id": 20
    },
    {
      "front": "Goodbye",
      "back": "Sayonara",
      "deckId": 16,
      "id": 21
    },
    {
      "front": "Good morning",
      "back": "Oyaho Gosaimasu",
      "deckId": 16,
      "id": 22
    },
    {
      "front": "Eat up!",
      "back": "Itadakemasu!",
      "deckId": 16,
      "id": 23
    },
    {
      "front": "Sorry",
      "back": "Simosen/Gomenesai",
      "deckId": 16,
      "id": 24
    },
    {
      "front": "One",
      "back": "1",
      "deckId": 12,
      "id": 25
    },
    {
      "front": "Two",
      "back": "2",
      "deckId": 12,
      "id": 26
    },
    {
      "front": "Three",
      "back": "3",
      "deckId": 12,
      "id": 27
    },
    {
      "front": "Four",
      "back": "4",
      "deckId": 12,
      "id": 28
    },
    {
      "front": "You",
      "back": "Ne-ga",
      "deckId": 17,
      "id": 29
    },
    {
      "front": "Seesaw",
      "back": "Shiso",
      "deckId": 17,
      "id": 30
    },
    {
      "front": "I love you",
      "back": "Salanghae",
      "deckId": 17,
      "id": 31
    },
    {
      "front": "Really?",
      "back": "Chincha?",
      "deckId": 17,
      "id": 32
    },
    {
      "front": "I miss you",
      "back": "Bogo shipda",
      "deckId": 17,
      "id": 33
    }
  ]
}